<dashboard script="autodiscover.js">
<label>Overview</label>
    <row>
    	<panel>
			<html>
				<div class = "splunk-view" data-require = "app/SplunkForPCAP/components/scc_takethetour/scc_takethetour"
					data-options = '{
						"user_slides":"scc-takethetour-slides",
						"width":"60",
						"title":"How to work with Splunk PCAP Analyzer?",
						"close_btn_label":"Close",
						"no_more_label":"Do not show this again",
						"cookie_name_suffix":"splunkforpcap",
						"hide_container":false,
						"show_credits":true
					}'>
				</div>
				<ul id="scc-takethetour-slides" class="hide">
					<li>
						<h3>Getting started - Requirements!</h3>
						Step 1: Make sure the ../SplunkForPCAP/bin/ folder has all administrative privileges to execute the batch and shell script<br />
						Step 2: Make sure you have tshark installed (delivered with Wireshark)<br />
						Step 3: Make sure you have set SPLUNK_HOME variable<br />
                        <br /><br />
                        <b>Click on the next slide and check how to configure the PCAP File Location!</b>
                        <br /><br />
					</li>
					<li>
						<h3>Getting started - PCAP File Location!</h3>
						To allow Splunk to collect your PCAP Files you have to specify where you have stored your pcap files.<br />
						You can specify your location in the Data Inputs (via Settings) --> PCAP File Location.<br />
						<div style="text-align: left;">
                            <img src="../../static/app/SplunkForPCAP/take_the_tour/datainputs.png" alt="datainputs.png"/>
                        </div>
                        <div style="text-align: left;">
                            <img src="../../static/app/SplunkForPCAP/take_the_tour/datainputs2.png" alt="datainputs2.png"/>
                        </div>
                        <br /><br />
                        <b>Click on the next slide to understand what happens with your pcap files after they are indexed!</b>
                        <br /><br />
					</li>
					<li>
						<h3>Getting started - Notes about the data!</h3>
						1. Sourcetype defined for indexing that data is "pcap:csv"<br />
						2. You will recognize that after you can see your pcap file indexed in Splunk it is removed from your folder. The new location of the PCAP File is: $SPLUNK_HOME\var\log\pcap\PCAPConverted. That is happening to avoid that the automatic script converts your pcap file twice.<br />
                        <br /><br />
					</li>
					<li>
						<h3>Analysis</h3>
						The App includes Dashboards which will show you:<br />
						- The Top Talker IP's, Protocols, VLANs, Conversations<br />
						- Detailed overview about IP Conversations, Packet Loss, TCP Error's, Round Trip Time<br />
						- Conversation Sankey Diagram (by Packets, by Bytes, by Destination Port) <br />
						- Microburst Dashboard (Bit timechart)<br />
						- DNS / NFS / HTTP / Keep Alive Communication Dashboards<br />
						- Hop Calculator between two IP's<br />
                        <br /><br />
					</li>
					<li>
						<h3>Thanks for downloading PCAP Analyzer for Splunk!</h3>
						<b>I hope the application can help you to analyze your problem in a better way and maybe even give you the right hint to the solution!</b>
						<br />
						<br />
						<b>ROADMAP</b><br />
						Support for more protocols and more use cases<br />
						Dashboards will change to highlight the most important use cases for troubleshooting.<br />
                        <br /><br />
					</li>

                </ul>
			</html>
		</panel>
	</row>
	<row>
    <html src="overview.html" />
    </row>
</dashboard>